

## Renmark Marte

\* E-mail: renmark.m@gmail.com

\* Mobile: +614 5249 4137

\* Portfolio: <a href="https://renmarkmarte.github.io">https://renmarkmarte.github.io</a>

\* LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/renmarte/

Driven graphic designer bringing forth valuable experience in design and communication with a passion for continuous learning and improvement. Goal oriented and is accustomed to working collaboratively in teams to produce desired results. Graduated with a computer science and design dual degree and is well-versed in both technical and creative thinking.

### **Key Skills:**

- \* Graphic design (print & digital)
- \* Visual communication
- \* Team collaboration

- \* Technical thinking
- \* Client engagement/customer service
- \* Proficient in computers

### -- WORK EXPERIENCE



### Graphic Designer/Prepress Automation Specialist @ Easy Signs, Smeaton Grange

(February 2018 - present)

- \* Provided design and artwork services for customers requiring signage with a standard 1-hour response time. Accurately followed customer instructions and brand guidelines for companies such as LJ Hooker, Ray White, and Anytime Fitness to produce designs across our wide range of products (57 in total).
- \* Developed automated workflows that processed customer orders using my technical background. This helped the design team process orders more quickly and efficiently with minimal human intervention, growing our monthly job approval average from 100 to 350 approvals per day over the course of 3 years.
- \* Collaborated closely with the design team and other departments (sales and production) to ensure that all orders were processed smoothly and problems were overcome to meet tight deadlines most of our products have 1 day lead times.
- \* Effectively communicated with customers over the phone or via email in a friendly and clear manner to provide a 5 star experience and bring their design ideas to life.



### Digital Design Intern @ DMG (Digital Media Group), Milsons Point

(June 2017 - October 2017)

- \* Developed UX/UI designs for desktop and mobile applications using UX processes, which involved undertaking extensive user research (user personas and wireframing) to ensure the developed designs were suited for the appropriate audience.
- \* Conceptualised design assets such as logos, display banners, images, presentations and wireframes for a wide range of projects while adhering to the company's design process workflow.
- \* Worked in an agile environment where strong team collaboration, adapting to constant changes, and juggling multiple projects at once was a must.
- \* Directly collaborated with clients and stakeholders to bring their design visions to fruition. This involved conducting weekly workshops with clients and the creative director to gather and implement feedback, and providing support through phone calls or emails to maintain client relationships.

### -- EDUCATION -

# Bachelor of Media Arts (Hons) / Bachelor of Computer Science University of New South Wales, Sydney

(2013 - 2017)

- \* Member of the Dean's Honours List 2017
- \* Received a Distinction average (82) in Graphics Media studio
- \* Graduated with a Distinction average, High School ATAR: 95.70

### -- SKILLS

### **Software:**

- \* Adobe Photoshop
- \* Adobe Illustrator
- \* Adobe InDesign
- \* Microsoft Office

### **Programming Languages:**

- \* JavaScript (React)
- \* Iava
- \* HTML5
- \* CSS

### -- PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES -

- \* Creative thinker Always tries to conceptualise design solutions that are creative, user-centred, and of high quality.
- \* Independent worker Self-driven, motivated, and can tackle tasks independently when required. Also not afraid of seeking feedback from colleagues for improvement.
- \* Team player Encourages and understands the importance of a supportive and cooperative team environment. Actively engages team members to communicate with each other and jointly solve issues and problems to achieve the desired goal.
- \* Effective communicator Articulate communicator with an appreciation for different communication styles when working with multiple departments and stakeholders. Can clearly communicate complex concepts to individuals or groups while also listening to and understanding the opinions of others.
- \* Results oriented Effectively uses expertise to successfully achieve expected goals while keeping within business expectations and budgets.
- \* Effective time management Can effectively manage multiple tasks at once while keeping a high standard of work through the use of time management tools to ensure that projects are appropriately prioritised and completed on time.
- \* Excellent customer service Dedicated to providing excellent customer service and maintaining stakeholder relationships.
- \* Proficient in computers

### -- HOBBIES & INTERESTS

- \* Art & design
- \* New technologies
- \* Travel

- \* Cooking and baking
- \* Hiking
- \* Gardening